bigboss-financial.com 2019-04-06

# Big Boss - Trade Forex on up to 555 Leverage and CFD

## Privacy Statement

Big Boss Holdings Company Limited takes your personal information and online privacy seriously to maintain your trust in our company and our services.  
Our privacy statement describes how we collect, utilize and protect information about you during your visit on our website.

__**What Information Does Big Boss Holdings Company Limited Collect Online？**

For statistical purpose, we collect the following information when you visit our website:

* Your IP address
* Number of visitors of our website
* Access date and time
* Which page did you access
* What files did you download
* Which browser did you use

We never use the above collected information to personally identify individual users.

__**What and When Do Big Boss Holdings Company Limited Collect My Personal Information Online?**

We collect personal information about you from the information you provide to us when you fill out an account application form on our website. The information we collect includes:

* Name
* Gender
* Date of Birth
* Nationality
* Address
* Telephone number
* Email address
* Account password

In addition, you will need to provide identity documents and address proof when you withdraw funds from your account for the first time.

Please note that as Big Boss Holdings Company Limited strictly follows rules and regulations against money laundering and terrorism, there is a chance that customers may be required to submit additional personal information. 

__**How Can I Review, Change or Correct Information You Collect?**

We are committed to maintaining accurate and up-to-date information on all of our customers. 

We may provide you with access to account information in different ways, for example, over the telephone or online. 

You may also require us to disclose information collected from you, amend your personal information and suspend/delete your account.

For details, please see the below " Client Agreement for Leveraged foreign exchange trading account”

[Client Agreement for Leveraged foreign exchange trading account](https://www.bigboss-financial.com/docs/view/agreement.pdf)

__**Does Big Boss Holdings Company Limited Use Cookies or Other Online Technologies to Collect Information About Me?**

We assure that we will not use Cookie or Web Beacon which is hard to be recognized by customers for collecting personal information. 

__**Does Big Boss Holdings Company Limited Share Personal Information About Me?**

Big Boss Holdings Company Limited will not disclose customers' personal information to third parties except in the following situations:

* If the customer agreed to do so. 
* Our trusted service providers need your personal information for their use in providing you with the products and services you have requested.
* If it is to protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Big Boss Holdings Company Limited, our other customers or the public as required or permitted by law.
* If it is required to disclose or provide by law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.

__**How Do You Protect Personal Information?**

We restrict access to the information obtained from our websites and web pages to our employees and related trustworthy service providers.

We are committed to ensuring that we take secure measures to prevent against information leak, damage and lost.

Please note that we will not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly for any losses caused by internet delay/transmission problems when customers contact us through internet. 

__**Will Big Boss Holdings Company Limited Make Changes To This Privacy Statement?**

This statement is effective February 1, 2017 and remains in effect until amended.

Big Boss Holdings Company Limited reserves the right to amend this Privacy Statement or alter its privacy principles at its sole discretion without notice to you.

Any alterations to this Privacy Statement or our privacy principles will be posted on our web site in a timely manner.
